Exhibit	NN	O
24	NN	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
MEN	NN	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
make	VB	O
,	VB	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
M	NN	PER
Longhi	NN	PER
,	NN	O
D	NN	PER
B	NN	PER
Burritt	NN	PER
and	CC	O
G	NN	PER
A	DT	PER
Zovko	NN	PER
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
one	CD	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
my	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
and	CC	O
execute	NN	O
for	IN	O
me	PRP	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
my	PRP$	O
behalf	NN	O
United	NNP	COMP
States	NN	COMP
Steel	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	NN	DATE
31	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2013	NN	DATE
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	NN	ORG
and	CC	ORG
Exchange	NNP	ORG
Commission	NNP	ORG
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
to	TO	O
such	JJ	O
report	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	NN	ORG
and	CC	ORG
Exchange	NNP	ORG
Commission	NNP	ORG
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
,	IN	O
in	IN	O
such	JJ	O
form	NN	O
as	IN	O
they	PRP	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
one	CD	O
or	CC	O
more	RBR	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
may	MD	O
approve	VB	O
,	VB	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
do	VB	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
other	JJ	O
acts	JJ	O
which	WDT	O
said	VBD	O
attorneys-in-fact	VBD	O
may	MD	O
deem	NN	O
necessary	JJ	O
or	CC	O
desirable	JJ	O
to	TO	O
enable	JJ	O
United	NNP	COMP
States	NN	COMP
Steel	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
to	TO	O
comply	NN	O
with	IN	O
said	VBD	O
Act	NNP	O
and	CC	O
the	DT	O
rules	DT	O
and	CC	O
regulations	CC	O
thereunder	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Dan	NNP	WITNESS
O	NN	WITNESS
Dinges	NN	WITNESS
Dan	NNP	O
O	NN	O
Dinges	NN	O
CORNING	NN	COMP
INCORPORATED	NN	COMP
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
,	NN	O
that	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
director	NN	O
and	CC	O
/	CC	O
or	CC	O
officer	NN	O
of	IN	O
Corning	VBG	COMP
Incorporated	VBN	COMP
,	VBN	O
a	DT	O
New	NNP	O
York	NNP	O
corporation	NN	O
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
make	VB	O
,	VB	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
James	NN	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Flaws	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Lewis	NNP	PER
A	DT	PER
.	NN	PER
Steverson	NN	PER
and	CC	O
R	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Tony	NN	PER
Tripeny	NN	PER
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
one	CD	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
Exhibit	NN	O
24	NN	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
MEN	NN	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
make	VB	O
,	VB	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
M	NN	PER
Longhi	NN	PER
,	NN	O
D	NN	PER
B	NN	PER
Burritt	NN	PER
and	CC	O
G	NN	PER
A	DT	PER
Zovko	NN	PER
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
one	CD	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
my	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
and	CC	O
execute	NN	O
for	IN	O
me	PRP	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
my	PRP$	O
behalf	NN	O
United	NNP	COMP
States	NN	COMP
Steel	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	NN	DATE
31	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2013	NN	DATE
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	NN	ORG
and	CC	ORG
Exchange	NNP	ORG
Commission	NNP	ORG
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
to	TO	O
such	JJ	O
report	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	NN	ORG
and	CC	ORG
Exchange	NNP	ORG
Commission	NNP	ORG
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
,	IN	O
in	IN	O
such	JJ	O
form	NN	O
as	IN	O
they	PRP	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
one	CD	O
or	CC	O
more	RBR	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
may	MD	O
approve	VB	O
,	VB	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
do	VB	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
other	JJ	O
acts	JJ	O
which	WDT	O
said	VBD	O
attorneys-in-fact	VBD	O
may	MD	O
deem	NN	O
necessary	JJ	O
or	CC	O
desirable	JJ	O
to	TO	O
enable	JJ	O
United	NNP	COMP
States	NN	COMP
Steel	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
to	TO	O
comply	NN	O
with	IN	O
said	VBD	O
Act	NNP	O
and	CC	O
the	DT	O
rules	DT	O
and	CC	O
regulations	CC	O
thereunder	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Dan	NNP	WITNESS
O	NN	WITNESS
Dinges	NN	WITNESS
Dan	NNP	O
O	NN	O
Dinges	NN	O
CORNING	NN	COMP
INCORPORATED	NN	COMP
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
,	NN	O
that	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
director	NN	O
and	CC	O
/	CC	O
or	CC	O
officer	NN	O
of	IN	O
Corning	VBG	COMP
Incorporated	VBN	COMP
,	VBN	O
a	DT	O
New	NNP	O
York	NNP	O
corporation	NN	O
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
make	VB	O
,	VB	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
James	NN	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Flaws	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Lewis	NNP	PER
A	DT	PER
.	NN	PER
Steverson	NN	PER
and	CC	O
R	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Tony	NN	PER
Tripeny	NN	PER
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
one	CD	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
and	CC	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
name	NN	O
,	NN	O
place	NN	O
and	CC	O
stead	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
and	CC	O
affix	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
name	NN	O
as	IN	O
director	NN	O
and	CC	O
/	CC	O
or	CC	O
officer	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
to	TO	O
(	TO	O
1	TO	O
)	TO	O
a	DT	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
,	NN	O
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
(	IN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
1934	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
”	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
fiscal	JJ	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	VBN	O
31	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
2013	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
or	CC	O
other	JJ	O
applicable	JJ	O
form	NN	O
,	NN	O
including	NN	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
exhibits	DT	O
,	DT	O
schedules	DT	O
,	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
,	DT	O
supplements	DT	O
and	CC	O
supporting	VBG	O
documents	VBG	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
by	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
and	CC	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Commission	NNP	O
(	NNP	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
”	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
as	IN	O
required	IN	O
under	IN	O
the	DT	O
1934	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
;	NNP	O
(	NNP	O
2	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
one	CD	O
or	CC	O
more	RBR	O
Registration	NN	O
Statements	NN	O
,	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
S	NN	O
-	NN	O
8	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
other	JJ	O
applicable	JJ	O
forms	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
,	DT	O
including	DT	O
post-effective	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
,	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
by	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
in	IN	O
connection	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
registration	NN	O
under	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1933	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
(	IN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
1933	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
”	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
of	IN	O
securities	IN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
file	NN	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
all	DT	O
exhibits	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
and	CC	O
other	JJ	O
supporting	VBG	O
documents	VBG	O
,	VBG	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
;	NNP	O
and	CC	O
(	CC	O
3	CC	O
)	CC	O
one	CD	O
or	CC	O
more	RBR	O
Registration	NN	O
Statements	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
S	NN	O
-	NN	O
3	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
other	JJ	O
applicable	JJ	O
forms	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
establishing	JJ	O
a	DT	O
universal	NN	O
shelf	NN	O
under	IN	O
Rule	NN	O
415	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
1933	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
or	CC	O
supplements	CC	O
thereto	NN	O
(	NN	O
including	NN	O
post-effective	NN	O
amendments	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
Registration	NN	O
Statements	NN	O
relating	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
offering	NN	O
of	IN	O
securities	IN	O
that	IN	O
are	VBP	O
filed	VBP	O
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
Rule	NN	O
462	NN	O
(	NN	O
b	NN	O
)	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
1933	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
file	NN	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
all	DT	O
exhibits	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
and	CC	O
other	JJ	O
supporting	VBG	O
documents	VBG	O
,	VBG	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
has	DT	O
subscribed	DT	O
these	DT	O
presents	DT	O
this	DT	O
5th	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
February	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2014	NN	DATE
.	IN	O

/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
John	NN	WITNESS
Seely	RB	WITNESS
Brown	NNP	WITNESS
John	NN	WITNESS
Seely	RB	WITNESS
Brown	NNP	WITNESS
CORNING	NN	O
INCORPORATED	NN	O
-	NN	O
2013	NN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
1	NNP	O
EX	NN	O
-	NN	O
24	NN	O
2	NN	O
exhibit24	NN	O
.	NN	O

htm	NN	O
EXHIBIT	NN	O
24	NN	O
Exhibit	NN	O
24	NN	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
With	IN	O
respect	NN	O
to	TO	O
holdings	TO	O
of	IN	O
and	CC	O
transactions	CC	O
in	IN	O
securities	IN	O
issued	IN	O
by	IN	O
Selecta	NN	COMP
Biosciences	NN	COMP
,	NN	COMP
Inc	NN	COMP
.	NN	COMP
(	IN	O
the	DT	O
"	DT	O
Company	NN	O
"	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
hereby	NN	O
constitutes	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoints	CC	O
the	DT	O
individuals	DT	O
named	DT	O
on	IN	O
Schedule	NN	O
A	DT	O
attached	VBN	O
hereto	NN	O
and	CC	O
as	IN	O
may	MD	O
be	VB	O
amended	VB	O
from	IN	O
time	NN	O
to	TO	O
time	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
signing	PRP	O
singly	RB	O
,	RB	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
and	CC	O
resubstitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
act	NN	O
as	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned's	DT	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
to	TO	O
:	TO	O
1	TO	O
.	TO	O

prepare	NN	O
,	NN	O
execute	NN	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned's	DT	O
name	NN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned's	DT	O
behalf	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
submit	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
United	NNP	O
States	NNP	O
Securities	NNP	O
and	CC	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Commission	NNP	O
(	NNP	O
the	DT	O
"	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
"	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
a	DT	O
Form	NN	O
ID	NN	O
,	NN	O
including	NN	O
amendments	NN	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
other	JJ	O
documents	JJ	O
necessary	JJ	O
or	CC	O
appropriate	NN	O
to	TO	O
obtain	VB	O
and	CC	O
/	CC	O
or	CC	O
regenerate	NN	O
codes	NN	O
and	CC	O
passwords	CC	O
enabling	CC	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
to	TO	O
make	VB	O
electronic	JJ	O
filings	NNS	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
of	IN	O
reports	IN	O
required	IN	O
by	IN	O
Section	NN	O
16	NN	O
(	NN	O
a	DT	O
)	DT	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
,	IN	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
rule	NN	O
or	CC	O
regulation	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
;	NNP	O
2	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

do	VB	O
and	CC	O
perform	NN	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
acts	DT	O
for	IN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
behalf	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
which	WDT	O
may	MD	O
be	VB	O
necessary	JJ	O
or	CC	O
desirable	JJ	O
to	TO	O
complete	JJ	O
and	CC	O
execute	NN	O
any	DT	O
such	JJ	O
Form	NN	O
3	NN	O
,	NN	O
4	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
5	CC	O
,	CC	O
complete	JJ	O
and	CC	O
execute	NN	O
any	DT	O
amendment	NN	O
or	CC	O
amendments	CC	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
timely	RB	O
file	NN	O
such	JJ	O
form	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
stock	NN	O
exchange	NN	O
or	CC	O
similar	JJ	O
authority	NN	O
;	NN	O
and	CC	O
4	CC	O
.	CC	O

take	VB	O
any	DT	O
other	JJ	O
action	NN	O
of	IN	O
any	DT	O
type	NN	O
whatsoever	NN	O
in	IN	O
connection	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
which	WDT	O
,	WDT	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
opinion	NN	O
of	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
may	MD	O
be	VB	O
of	IN	O
benefit	NN	O
to	TO	O
,	TO	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
best	JJS	O
interest	NN	O
of	IN	O
,	IN	O
or	CC	O
legally	RB	O
required	RB	O
by	IN	O
,	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
it	PRP	O
being	VBG	O
understood	NN	O
that	IN	O
the	DT	O
documents	DT	O
executed	VBN	O
by	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
on	IN	O
behalf	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
this	DT	O
Power	NN	O
of	IN	O
Attorney	NN	O
shall	MD	O
be	VB	O
in	IN	O
such	JJ	O
form	NN	O
and	CC	O
shall	MD	O
contain	NN	O
such	JJ	O
terms	JJ	O
and	CC	O
conditions	CC	O
as	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
may	MD	O
approve	VB	O
in	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact's	JJ	O
discretion	NN	O
.	NN	O

CAMPBELL	NN	COMP
SOUP	NN	COMP
COMPANY	NN	COMP
Signature	NN	O
Dated	NN	O
as	IN	O
of	IN	O
September	NN	DATE
25	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2013	NN	DATE
/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Edmund	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Carpenter	NNP	WITNESS
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Charles	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Perrin	NN	WITNESS
Edmund	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Carpenter	NNP	WITNESS
Charles	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Perrin	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Paul	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Charron	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Barry	NNP	WITNESS
Rand	NN	WITNESS
Paul	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Charron	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Barry	NNP	WITNESS
Rand	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Bennett	NN	WITNESS
Dorrance	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Nick	NN	WITNESS
Shreiber	NN	WITNESS
Bennett	NN	WITNESS
Dorrance	NN	WITNESS
Nick	NN	WITNESS
Shreiber	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Lawrence	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Karlson	NN	WITNESS
/	SYM	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Tracey	NN	WITNESS
T	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Travis	NN	WITNESS
Lawrence	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Karlson	NN	WITNESS
Tracey	NN	WITNESS
T	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Travis	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Randall	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Larrimore	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Archbold	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
van	NN	WITNESS
Beuren	NN	WITNESS
Randall	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Larrimore	NN	WITNESS
Archbold	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
van	NN	WITNESS
Beuren	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Mary	NNP	WITNESS
Alice	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Malone	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Les	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Vinney	NN	WITNESS
Mary	NNP	WITNESS
Alice	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Malone	NN	WITNESS
Les	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Vinney	NN	WITNESS
/	SYM	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Sara	NN	WITNESS
Mathew	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Charlotte	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Weber	NNP	WITNESS
Sara	NN	WITNESS
Mathew	NN	WITNESS
Charlotte	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Weber	NNP	WITNESS
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Denise	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Morrison	NN	WITNESS
Denise	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Morrison	NN	WITNESS
EX	NN	O
-	NN	O
24	NN	O
9	NN	O
wfc	NN	O
-	NN	O
12312017xex24	NN	O
.	NN	O

htm	NN	O
EXHIBIT	NN	O
24	NN	O
Exhibit	NN	O
24	NN	O
WELLS	NN	COMP
FARGO	NN	COMP
&	NN	COMP
COMPANY	NN	COMP
Power	NN	O
of	IN	O
Attorney	NN	O
of	IN	O
Director	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
MEN	NN	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
,	NN	O
that	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
director	NN	O
of	IN	O
WELLS	IN	O
FARGO	IN	O
&	IN	O
COMPANY	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
make	VB	O
,	VB	O
constitute	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
JAMES	NN	PER
H	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
QUIGLEY	NN	PER
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
director	NN	O
and	CC	O
Chairman	NNP	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Audit	NN	O
and	CC	O
Examination	NN	O
Committee	NNP	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Board	NNP	O
of	IN	O
Directors	IN	O
,	IN	O
and	CC	O
JOHN	NN	PER
D	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
BAKER	NN	PER
II	NN	PER
,	NN	O
THEODORE	NN	PER
F	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
CRAVER	NN	PER
,	NN	O
JR	NN	O
.	NN	O

,	NN	O
FEDERICO	NN	PER
F	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
PEÑA	NN	PER
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
RONALD	NN	PER
L	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
SARGENT	NN	PER
,	NN	O
directors	NN	O
and	CC	O
members	CC	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Audit	NN	O
and	CC	O
Examination	NN	O
Committee	NNP	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Board	NNP	O
of	IN	O
Directors	IN	O
,	IN	O
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
and	CC	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
name	NN	O
,	NN	O
place	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
stead	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
and	CC	O
affix	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
name	NN	O
as	IN	O
such	JJ	O
director	NN	O
of	IN	O
said	VBD	O
Company	NN	O
to	TO	O
an	DT	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
fiscal	JJ	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	VBN	O
31	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
2017	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
by	IN	O
said	VBD	O
Company	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
and	CC	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Commission	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
Washington	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
D.C	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
has	DT	O
executed	VBN	O
this	DT	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
attorney	NN	O
this	DT	O
27th	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
February	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2018	NN	DATE
.	IN	O

/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JOHN	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
BAKER	NN	WITNESS
II	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
MARIA	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
MORRIS	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JOHN	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
CHEN	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
KAREN	NN	WITNESS
B	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
PEETZ	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
CELESTE	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
CLARK	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
FEDERICO	NN	WITNESS
F	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
PEÑA	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
THEODORE	NN	WITNESS
F	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
CRAVER	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
JR	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JUAN	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
PUJADAS	NN	WITNESS
/	DT	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
LLOYD	NN	WITNESS
H	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
DEAN	NNP	WITNESS
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JAMES	NN	WITNESS
H	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
QUIGLEY	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ELIZABETH	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
DUKE	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
RONALD	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
SARGENT	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ENRIQUE	NN	WITNESS
HERNANDEZ	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
JR	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
TIMOTHY	NN	WITNESS
J	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
SLOAN	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
DONALD	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
JAMES	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
SUZANNE	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
VAUTRINOT	NN	WITNESS
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JAMES	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
BARKSDALE	NN	WITNESS
James	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Barksdale	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
MISSISSIPPI	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
MADISON	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Sharon	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Lucius	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
James	NN	PER
L	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Barksdale	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
SHARON	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
LUCIUS	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
October	NN	DATE
15	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2013	NN	DATE
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JOHN	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
EDWARDSON	NN	WITNESS
John	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Edwardson	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Anne	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Coleman	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
John	NN	PER
A	DT	PER
.	NN	PER
Edwardson	NN	PER
,	DT	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ANNE	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
COLEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
9	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
18	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NN	PER
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
I	PRP	O
have	VB	O
hereunto	NN	O
set	NN	O
my	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
this	DT	O
16th	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
June	NNP	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2010	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JUDITH	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
ESTRIN	NN	WITNESS
Judith	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Estrin	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
CALIFORNIA	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SAN	NN	O
MATEO	NN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Steven	RB	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Wagner	NN	WITNESS
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Judith	NN	PER
L	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Estrin	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
she	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
her	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
STEVEN	NN	PER
A	DT	PER
.	NN	PER
WAGNER	NN	PER
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
7	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
1	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
13	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
J.R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
HYDE	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
III	NN	WITNESS
J	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Hyde	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
III	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Melissa	NN	WITNESS
Fleck	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
J	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
R	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Hyde	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
III	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
MELISSA	NN	WITNESS
FLECK	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
8	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
22	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
2010	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
SHIRLEY	NN	WITNESS
ANN	NN	WITNESS
JACKSON	NN	WITNESS
Shirley	NN	WITNESS
Ann	NN	WITNESS
Jackson	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
NEW	NN	O
YORK	NN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
RENSSELAER	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Theresa	NN	WITNESS
Hobbs	NN	WITNESS
,	PRP	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Shirley	NN	PER
Ann	NN	PER
Jackson	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
she	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
her	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Theresa	NN	WITNESS
Hobbs	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
12	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
27	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
STEVEN	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
LORANGER	NN	WITNESS
Steven	RB	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Loranger	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Anne	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Coleman	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Steven	RB	PER
R	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Loranger	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ANNE	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
COLEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
9	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
18	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
I	PRP	O
have	VB	O
hereunto	NN	O
set	NN	O
my	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
this	DT	O
2nd	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
June	NNP	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2010	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
GARY	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
LOVEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Gary	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Loveman	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Anne	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Coleman	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Gary	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Loveman	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ANNE	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
COLEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
9	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
18	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
SUSAN	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
SCHWAB	NN	WITNESS
Susan	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Schwab	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Anne	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Coleman	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Susan	NN	PER
C	SYM	PER
.	NN	PER
Schwab	NN	PER
,	SYM	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
she	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
her	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ANNE	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
COLEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
9	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
18	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JOSHUA	NN	WITNESS
I	PRP	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
SMITH	NN	WITNESS
Joshua	NN	WITNESS
I	PRP	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Smith	NNP	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
MARYLAND	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
MONTGOMERY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Chaminda	NN	WITNESS
Dodangoda	NN	WITNESS
,	PRP	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Joshua	NN	PER
I	PRP	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
CHAMINDA	NN	WITNESS
DODANGODA	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
04	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
01	NNP	O
/	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	PER
.	NN	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
I	PRP	O
have	VB	O
hereunto	NN	O
set	NN	O
my	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
this	DT	O
7th	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
June	NNP	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2010	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
DAVID	NN	WITNESS
P	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
STEINER	NN	WITNESS
David	NN	WITNESS
P	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Steiner	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Anne	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Coleman	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
David	NN	PER
P	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Steiner	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ANNE	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
COLEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
9	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
18	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NN	PER
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
and	CC	O
John	NN	PER
L	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Merino	NN	PER
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
and	CC	O
resubstitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
his	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
and	CC	O
agents	CC	O
,	CC	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
and	CC	O
authority	NN	O
to	TO	O
execute	NN	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
name	NN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
behalf	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
as	IN	O
such	JJ	O
Director	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
with	IN	O
respect	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
fiscal	JJ	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
May	NNP	O
31	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
2010	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
;	NN	O
and	CC	O
hereby	NN	O
ratifies	NN	O
and	CC	O
confirms	CC	O
all	DT	O
that	IN	O
said	VBD	O
attorneys-in-fact	VBD	O
and	CC	O
agents	CC	O
,	CC	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
or	CC	O
their	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
his	PRP$	O
substitute	NN	O
or	CC	O
substitutes	CC	O
may	MD	O
lawfully	RB	O
do	VB	O
or	CC	O
cause	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
done	VBN	O
by	IN	O
virtue	NN	O
of	IN	O
these	DT	O
presents	DT	O
.	DT	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
I	PRP	O
have	VB	O
hereunto	NN	O
set	NN	O
my	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
this	DT	O
21st	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
June	NNP	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2010	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
PAUL	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
WALSH	NN	WITNESS
Paul	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Walsh	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Anne	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Coleman	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Paul	NN	PER
S	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Walsh	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ANNE	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
COLEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
9	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
28	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
the	DT	O
principal	NN	O
financial	JJ	O
officer	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
and	CC	O
John	NN	PER
L	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Merino	NN	PER
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
and	CC	O
resubstitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
his	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
and	CC	O
agents	CC	O
,	CC	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
and	CC	O
authority	NN	O
to	TO	O
execute	NN	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
name	NN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
behalf	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
as	IN	O
such	JJ	O
officer	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
with	IN	O
respect	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
fiscal	JJ	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
May	NNP	O
31	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
2010	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
;	NN	O
and	CC	O
hereby	NN	O
ratifies	NN	O
and	CC	O
confirms	CC	O
all	DT	O
that	IN	O
said	VBD	O
attorneys-in-fact	VBD	O
and	CC	O
agents	CC	O
,	CC	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
or	CC	O
their	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
his	PRP$	O
substitute	NN	O
or	CC	O
substitutes	CC	O
may	MD	O
lawfully	RB	O
do	VB	O
or	CC	O
cause	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
done	VBN	O
by	IN	O
virtue	NN	O
of	IN	O
these	DT	O
presents	DT	O
.	DT	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
I	PRP	O
have	VB	O
hereunto	NN	O
set	NN	O
my	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
this	DT	O
1st	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
June	NNP	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2010	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ALAN	NN	WITNESS
B	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
GRAF	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
JR	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Alan	NNP	WITNESS
B	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Graf	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
Jr	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Anne	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Coleman	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
ANNE	NN	WITNESS
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
COLEMAN	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
9	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
28	NNP	O
-	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
the	DT	O
principal	NN	O
executive	NN	O
officer	NN	O
and	CC	O
a	DT	O
director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Jr	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
FREDERICK	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
SMITH	NN	WITNESS
Frederick	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Smith	NNP	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
June	NNP	WITNESS
Y	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Fitzgerald	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JUNE	NN	WITNESS
Y	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
FITZGERALD	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
August	NNP	O
22	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
2010	NNP	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
the	DT	O
principal	NN	O
accounting	NN	O
officer	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
and	CC	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	PER
.	NN	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
I	PRP	O
have	VB	O
hereunto	NN	O
set	NN	O
my	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
this	DT	O
1st	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
June	NNP	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2010	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JOHN	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
MERINO	NN	WITNESS
John	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Merino	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
TENNESSEE	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
SHELBY	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Carol	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Whitfield	NN	WITNESS
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
John	IN	O
L	NN	O
.	NN	O

Merino	NN	O
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
CAROL	NNP	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
WHITFIELD	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
Oct	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

5	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
Exhibit	NN	O
24	NN	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
,	NN	O
that	IN	O
each	DT	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
several	JJ	O
undersigned	JJ	O
officers	JJ	O
and	CC	O
directors	CC	O
whose	WP$	O
signatures	WP$	O
appear	VB	O
below	IN	O
,	IN	O
hereby	NN	O
makes	NN	O
,	NN	O
constitutes	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoints	CC	O
David	NN	PER
G	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Leitch	NN	PER
and	CC	O
Ross	NNP	PER
E	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Jeffries	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
acting	VBG	O
individually	RB	O
,	RB	O
his	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys	JJ	O
with	IN	O
power	NN	O
to	TO	O
act	NN	O
without	IN	O
any	DT	O
other	JJ	O
and	CC	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
prepare	NN	O
,	NN	O
execute	NN	O
,	NN	O
deliver	NN	O
and	CC	O
file	NN	O
in	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
name	NN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
behalf	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
in	IN	O
each	DT	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
officer	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
and	CC	O
director	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
capacity	NN	O
or	CC	O
capacities	CC	O
as	IN	O
shown	VBN	O
below	IN	O
,	IN	O
an	DT	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	VBN	O
31	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
2017	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
exhibits	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
documents	DT	O
in	IN	O
support	NN	O
thereof	NN	O
or	CC	O
supplemental	NN	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
or	CC	O
supplements	CC	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
,	VBG	O
hereby	NN	O
ratifying	NN	O
and	CC	O
confirming	VBG	O
all	DT	O
acts	DT	O
and	CC	O
things	CC	O
which	WDT	O
said	VBD	O
attorneys	VBD	O
or	CC	O
attorney	NN	O
might	MD	O
do	VB	O
or	CC	O
cause	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
done	VBN	O
by	IN	O
virtue	NN	O
hereof	NN	O
.	NN	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
each	DT	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
officers	DT	O
and	CC	O
directors	CC	O
,	CC	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
capacity	NN	O
or	CC	O
capacities	CC	O
noted	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
has	VBN	O
hereunto	NN	O
set	NN	O
his	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
as	IN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
date	NN	O
indicated	NN	O
below	IN	O
.	IN	O

Signature	NN	O
Title	NN	O
Date	NN	O
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Brian	NN	WITNESS
T	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Moynihan	NN	WITNESS
Chief	NN	O
Executive	NN	O
Officer	NN	O
,	NN	O
Chairman	NNP	O
and	CC	O
Director	NN	O
(	NN	O
Principal	NN	O
Executive	NN	O
Officer	NN	O
)	NN	O
February	NN	O
22	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Brian	NN	WITNESS
T	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Moynihan	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Paul	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Donofrio	NN	WITNESS
Chief	NN	O
Financial	JJ	O
Officer	NN	O
(	NN	O
Principal	NN	O
Financial	JJ	O
Officer	NN	O
)	NN	O
February	NN	DATE
22	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2018	NN	DATE
Paul	NN	WITNESS
M	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Donofrio	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Rudolf	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Bless	NN	WITNESS
Chief	NN	O
Accounting	NN	O
Officer	NN	O
(	NN	O
Principal	NN	O
Accounting	NN	O
Officer	NN	O
)	NN	O
February	NN	DATE
22	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2018	NN	DATE
Rudolf	NN	WITNESS
A	DT	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Bless	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Sharon	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Allen	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
19	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Sharon	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Allen	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Susan	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Bies	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	DATE
22	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2018	NN	DATE
Susan	NN	O
S	NN	O
.	NN	O

Bies	NN	O
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Jack	NNP	WITNESS
O	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Bovender	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
Jr	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	DATE
17	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2018	NN	DATE
Jack	NNP	WITNESS
O	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Bovender	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
Jr	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Frank	NNP	WITNESS
P	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Bramble	JJ	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
Sr	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	DATE
22	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2018	NN	DATE
Frank	NNP	WITNESS
P	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Bramble	JJ	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
Sr	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
/	JJ	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Pierre	NN	WITNESS
de	NNS	WITNESS
Weck	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
20	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Pierre	NN	WITNESS
de	NNS	WITNESS
Weck	NN	WITNESS
/	NNS	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Arnold	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Donald	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
22	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Arnold	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Donald	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Linda	NN	WITNESS
P	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Hudson	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
16	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Linda	NN	WITNESS
P	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Hudson	NN	WITNESS
Signature	NN	O
Title	NN	O
Date	NN	O
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Monica	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Lozano	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
17	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Monica	NN	WITNESS
C	SYM	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Lozano	NN	WITNESS
/	SYM	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Thomas	NN	WITNESS
J	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
May	NNP	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
19	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Thomas	NN	*
J	NN	*
.	NN	*
May	NNP	*
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Lionel	NNS	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Nowell	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
III	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
16	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Lionel	NNS	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Nowell	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	WITNESS
III	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Michael	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
White	NNP	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
21	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Michael	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
White	NNP	WITNESS
/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Thomas	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Woods	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
14	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Thomas	NN	WITNESS
D	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Woods	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
David	NN	WITNESS
Yost	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
19	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
R	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
David	NN	WITNESS
Yost	NN	WITNESS
/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Maria	NNS	WITNESS
T	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Zuber	NN	WITNESS
Director	NN	O
February	NN	O
15	NN	O
,	NN	O
2018	NN	O
Maria	NNS	WITNESS
T	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Zuber	NN	WITNESS
PPG	NN	COMP
INDUSTRIES	NN	COMP
,	NN	COMP
INC	NN	COMP
.	NN	COMP
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
(	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Stephen	PRP	O
F	NN	O
.	NN	O

Angel	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
PPG	NN	COMP
Industries	NN	COMP
,	IN	O
Inc	IN	O
.	IN	O

(	IN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Pennsylvania	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Charles	NN	PER
E	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Bunch	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Glenn	NN	PER
E	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Bost	NN	PER
II	NN	PER
and	CC	O
David	NN	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Navikas	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
my	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys	JJ	O
or	CC	O
attorneys-in-fact	CC	O
,	CC	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
and	CC	O
revocation	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
,	NN	O
in	IN	O
my	PRP$	O
name	NN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
my	PRP$	O
behalf	NN	O
as	IN	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
fiscal	JJ	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	VBN	O
31	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
2012	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
and	CC	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Commission	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
Washington	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
DC	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

WITNESS	NNP	O
my	PRP$	O
hand	NN	O
this	DT	O
21st	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
February	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2013	NN	DATE
.	IN	O

/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
STEPHEN	NN	WITNESS
F	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
ANGEL	NN	WITNESS
Stephen	NN	WITNESS
F	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Angel	NNP	WITNESS
CORNING	NN	COMP
INCORPORATED	NN	COMP
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
,	NN	O
that	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
director	NN	O
and	CC	O
/	CC	O
or	CC	O
officer	NN	O
of	IN	O
Corning	VBG	COMP
Incorporated	VBN	COMP
,	VBN	O
a	DT	O
New	NNP	O
York	NNP	O
corporation	NN	O
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
make	VB	O
,	VB	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
James	NN	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Flaws	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Lewis	NNP	PER
A	DT	PER
.	NN	PER
Steverson	NN	PER
and	CC	O
R	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Tony	NN	PER
Tripeny	NN	PER
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
one	CD	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
and	CC	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
name	NN	O
,	NN	O
place	NN	O
and	CC	O
stead	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
and	CC	O
affix	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
’	DT	O
s	NN	O
name	NN	O
as	IN	O
director	NN	O
and	CC	O
/	CC	O
or	CC	O
officer	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
to	TO	O
(	TO	O
1	TO	O
)	TO	O
a	DT	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
,	NN	O
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
(	IN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
1934	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
”	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
fiscal	JJ	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	VBN	O
31	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
2013	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
or	CC	O
other	JJ	O
applicable	JJ	O
form	NN	O
,	NN	O
including	NN	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
exhibits	DT	O
,	DT	O
schedules	DT	O
,	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
,	DT	O
supplements	DT	O
and	CC	O
supporting	VBG	O
documents	VBG	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
by	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
and	CC	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Commission	NNP	O
(	NNP	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
”	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
as	IN	O
required	IN	O
under	IN	O
the	DT	O
1934	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
;	NNP	O
(	NNP	O
2	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
one	CD	O
or	CC	O
more	RBR	O
Registration	NN	O
Statements	NN	O
,	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
S	NN	O
-	NN	O
8	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
other	JJ	O
applicable	JJ	O
forms	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
,	DT	O
including	DT	O
post-effective	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
,	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
by	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
in	IN	O
connection	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
registration	NN	O
under	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1933	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
(	IN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
1933	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
”	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
of	IN	O
securities	IN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
file	NN	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
all	DT	O
exhibits	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
and	CC	O
other	JJ	O
supporting	VBG	O
documents	VBG	O
,	VBG	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
;	NNP	O
and	CC	O
(	CC	O
3	CC	O
)	CC	O
one	CD	O
or	CC	O
more	RBR	O
Registration	NN	O
Statements	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
S	NN	O
-	NN	O
3	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
other	JJ	O
applicable	JJ	O
forms	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
establishing	JJ	O
a	DT	O
universal	NN	O
shelf	NN	O
under	IN	O
Rule	NN	O
415	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
1933	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
or	CC	O
supplements	CC	O
thereto	NN	O
(	NN	O
including	NN	O
post-effective	NN	O
amendments	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
Registration	NN	O
Statements	NN	O
relating	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
offering	NN	O
of	IN	O
securities	IN	O
that	IN	O
are	VBP	O
filed	VBP	O
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
Rule	NN	O
462	NN	O
(	NN	O
b	NN	O
)	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
1933	DT	O
Act	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
file	NN	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
with	IN	O
all	DT	O
exhibits	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
and	CC	O
other	JJ	O
supporting	VBG	O
documents	VBG	O
,	VBG	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
has	DT	O
subscribed	DT	O
these	DT	O
presents	DT	O
this	DT	O
5th	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
February	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2014	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
John	NN	WITNESS
Seely	RB	WITNESS
Brown	NNP	WITNESS
John	NN	WITNESS
Seely	RB	WITNESS
Brown	NNP	WITNESS
CORNING	NN	COMP
INCORPORATED	NN	COMP
-	NN	O
2013	NN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
1	NNP	O
EX	NN	O
-	NN	O
24	NN	O
2	NN	O
exhibit24	NN	O
.	NN	O

htm	NN	O
EXHIBIT	NN	O
24	NN	O
Exhibit	NN	O
24	NN	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
With	IN	O
respect	NN	O
to	TO	O
holdings	TO	O
of	IN	O
and	CC	O
transactions	CC	O
in	IN	O
securities	IN	O
issued	IN	O
by	IN	O
Selecta	NN	COMP
Biosciences	NN	COMP
,	NN	COMP
Inc	NN	COMP
.	NN	COMP
(	IN	O
the	DT	O
"	DT	O
Company	NN	O
"	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
hereby	NN	O
constitutes	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoints	CC	O
the	DT	O
individuals	DT	O
named	DT	O
on	IN	O
Schedule	NN	O
A	DT	O
attached	VBN	O
hereto	NN	O
and	CC	O
as	IN	O
may	MD	O
be	VB	O
amended	VB	O
from	IN	O
time	NN	O
to	TO	O
time	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
signing	PRP	O
singly	RB	O
,	RB	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
and	CC	O
resubstitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
act	NN	O
as	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned's	DT	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
to	TO	O
:	TO	O
1	TO	O
.	TO	O

prepare	NN	O
,	NN	O
execute	NN	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned's	DT	O
name	NN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned's	DT	O
behalf	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
submit	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
United	NNP	O
States	NNP	O
Securities	NNP	O
and	CC	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Commission	NNP	O
(	NNP	O
the	DT	O
"	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
"	NNP	O
)	NNP	O
a	DT	O
Form	NN	O
ID	NN	O
,	NN	O
including	NN	O
amendments	NN	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
other	JJ	O
documents	JJ	O
necessary	JJ	O
or	CC	O
appropriate	NN	O
to	TO	O
obtain	VB	O
and	CC	O
/	CC	O
or	CC	O
regenerate	NN	O
codes	NN	O
and	CC	O
passwords	CC	O
enabling	CC	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
to	TO	O
make	VB	O
electronic	JJ	O
filings	NNS	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
of	IN	O
reports	IN	O
required	IN	O
by	IN	O
Section	NN	O
16	NN	O
(	NN	O
a	DT	O
)	DT	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
,	IN	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
rule	NN	O
or	CC	O
regulation	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
;	NNP	O
2	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

do	VB	O
and	CC	O
perform	NN	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
acts	DT	O
for	IN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
behalf	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
which	WDT	O
may	MD	O
be	VB	O
necessary	JJ	O
or	CC	O
desirable	JJ	O
to	TO	O
complete	JJ	O
and	CC	O
execute	NN	O
any	DT	O
such	JJ	O
Form	NN	O
3	NN	O
,	NN	O
4	NN	O
,	NN	O
or	CC	O
5	CC	O
,	CC	O
complete	JJ	O
and	CC	O
execute	NN	O
any	DT	O
amendment	NN	O
or	CC	O
amendments	CC	O
thereto	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
timely	RB	O
file	NN	O
such	JJ	O
form	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
SEC	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
stock	NN	O
exchange	NN	O
or	CC	O
similar	JJ	O
authority	NN	O
;	NN	O
and	CC	O
4	CC	O
.	CC	O

take	VB	O
any	DT	O
other	JJ	O
action	NN	O
of	IN	O
any	DT	O
type	NN	O
whatsoever	NN	O
in	IN	O
connection	NN	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
which	WDT	O
,	WDT	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
opinion	NN	O
of	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
,	JJ	O
may	MD	O
be	VB	O
of	IN	O
benefit	NN	O
to	TO	O
,	TO	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
best	JJS	O
interest	NN	O
of	IN	O
,	IN	O
or	CC	O
legally	RB	O
required	RB	O
by	IN	O
,	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
it	PRP	O
being	VBG	O
understood	NN	O
that	IN	O
the	DT	O
documents	DT	O
executed	VBN	O
by	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
on	IN	O
behalf	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
this	DT	O
Power	NN	O
of	IN	O
Attorney	NN	O
shall	MD	O
be	VB	O
in	IN	O
such	JJ	O
form	NN	O
and	CC	O
shall	MD	O
contain	NN	O
such	JJ	O
terms	JJ	O
and	CC	O
conditions	CC	O
as	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
may	MD	O
approve	VB	O
in	IN	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact's	JJ	O
discretion	NN	O
.	NN	O

This	DT	O
Power	NN	O
of	IN	O
Attorney	NN	O
shall	MD	O
remain	NN	O
in	IN	O
full	JJ	O
force	NN	O
and	CC	O
effect	NN	O
until	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
is	VBZ	O
no	DT	O
longer	NN	O
required	NN	O
to	TO	O
file	NN	O
Forms	NN	O
3	NN	O
,	NN	O
4	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
5	CC	O
with	IN	O
respect	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
undersigned's	DT	O
holdings	DT	O
of	IN	O
and	CC	O
transactions	CC	O
in	IN	O
securities	IN	O
issued	IN	O
by	IN	O
Selecta	IN	O
Biosciences	IN	O
,	IN	O
Inc	IN	O
.	IN	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
I	PRP	O
have	VB	O
hereunto	NN	O
subscribed	NN	O
my	PRP$	O
name	NN	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
capacity	NN	O
(	NN	O
ies	NN	O
)	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
below	IN	O
this	DT	O
11th	NN	DATE
day	NN	DATE
of	IN	DATE
February	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2019	NN	DATE
.	NN	DATE
/	IN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Jeffrey	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Basch	NN	WITNESS
Jeffrey	NN	WITNESS
W	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Basch	NN	WITNESS
Vice	NNP	O
President	NNP	O
and	CC	O
Chief	NN	O
Accounting	NN	O
Officer	NN	O
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
MEN	NN	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
that	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
director	NN	O
of	IN	O
CULP	NN	COMP
,	NN	COMP
INC	NN	COMP
.	NN	COMP
,	IN	O
a	DT	O
North	NN	O
Carolina	NN	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
hereby	NN	O
constitutes	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoints	CC	O
KENNETH	NN	PER
R	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
BOWLING	NN	PER
the	DT	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
agent	NN	O
and	CC	O
attorney-in-fact	CC	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
as	IN	O
a	DT	O
director	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation's	NN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
April	VBN	O
30	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
2017	VBN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
filed	VB	O
with	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
and	CC	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Commission	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
Washington	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
D.C	NNP	O
.	NNP	O

,	NNP	O
under	IN	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
as	IN	O
amended	IN	O
,	IN	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
sign	NN	O
any	DT	O
amendment	NN	O
or	CC	O
amendments	CC	O
to	TO	O
such	JJ	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
,	NN	O
hereby	NN	O
ratifying	NN	O
and	CC	O
confirming	VBG	O
all	DT	O
acts	DT	O
taken	VBN	O
by	IN	O
such	JJ	O
agent	NN	O
and	CC	O
attorney-in-fact	CC	O
,	CC	O
as	IN	O
herein	NN	O
authorized	VBN	O
.	VBN	O

/	VBN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
Patrick	NN	WITNESS
B	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Flavin	NN	WITNESS
Patrick	NN	WITNESS
B	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Flavin	NN	WITNESS
Date	NN	O
:	NN	O
July	NN	DATE
14	NN	DATE
,	NN	DATE
2017	NN	DATE
POWER	NN	O
OF	IN	O
ATTORNEY	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
PERSONS	DT	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
,	DT	O
a	DT	O
Director	NN	O
of	IN	O
FedEx	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
(	NN	O
the	DT	O
“	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
”	NN	O
)	NN	O
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Delaware	DT	O
corporation	NN	O
,	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
hereby	NN	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Frederick	NN	PER
W	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Smith	NNP	PER
,	NNP	O
Alan	NNP	PER
B	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Graf	NN	PER
,	NN	PER
Jr	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
and	CC	O
John	NN	PER
L	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Merino	NN	PER
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
each	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
of	IN	O
substitution	NN	O
and	CC	O
resubstitution	NN	O
,	NN	O
his	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorneys-in-fact	JJ	O
and	CC	O
agents	CC	O
,	CC	O
with	IN	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
and	CC	O
authority	NN	O
to	TO	O
execute	NN	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
name	NN	O
and	CC	O
on	IN	O
behalf	NN	O
of	IN	O
the	DT	O
undersigned	DT	O
as	IN	O
such	JJ	O
Director	NN	O
,	NN	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
with	IN	O
respect	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Corporation	NN	O
’	NN	O
s	NN	O
fiscal	JJ	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
May	NNP	O
31	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
2010	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
and	CC	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
thereto	NN	O
;	NN	O
and	CC	O
hereby	NN	O
ratifies	NN	O
and	CC	O
confirms	CC	O
all	DT	O
that	IN	O
said	VBD	O
attorneys-in-fact	VBD	O
and	CC	O
agents	CC	O
,	CC	O
or	CC	O
any	DT	O
of	IN	O
them	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
or	CC	O
their	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
his	PRP$	O
substitute	NN	O
or	CC	O
substitutes	CC	O
may	MD	O
lawfully	RB	O
do	VB	O
or	CC	O
cause	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
done	VBN	O
by	IN	O
virtue	NN	O
of	IN	O
these	DT	O
presents	DT	O
.	DT	O

/	NNP	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
JAMES	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
BARKSDALE	NN	WITNESS
James	NN	WITNESS
L	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Barksdale	NN	WITNESS
STATE	NN	O
OF	IN	O
MISSISSIPPI	IN	O
COUNTY	NN	O
OF	IN	O
MADISON	IN	O
I	PRP	O
,	PRP	O
Sharon	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
Lucius	NN	WITNESS
,	NN	O
a	DT	O
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
in	IN	O
and	CC	O
for	IN	O
said	VBD	O
County	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
aforesaid	NN	O
State	NN	O
,	NN	O
do	VB	O
hereby	NN	O
certify	NN	O
that	IN	O
James	NN	PER
L	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Barksdale	NN	PER
,	NN	O
personally	RB	O
known	VBN	O
to	TO	O
me	PRP	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
the	DT	O
same	JJ	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
subscribed	VBZ	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
foregoing	VBG	O
instrument	NN	O
,	NN	O
appeared	NN	O
before	IN	O
me	PRP	O
this	DT	O
day	NN	O
in	IN	O
person	NN	O
,	NN	O
and	CC	O
acknowledged	VBD	O
that	IN	O
he	PRP	O
signed	PRP	O
and	CC	O
delivered	CC	O
the	DT	O
said	VBD	O
instrument	NN	O
as	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
free	JJ	O
and	CC	O
voluntary	JJ	O
act	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
uses	DT	O
and	CC	O
purposes	CC	O
therein	NN	O
set	NN	O
forth	NN	O
.	NN	O

/	NN	O
s	NN	O
/	NN	O
SHARON	NN	WITNESS
S	NN	WITNESS
.	NN	WITNESS
LUCIUS	NN	WITNESS
Notary	JJ	O
Public	JJ	O
My	PRP$	O
Commission	NNP	O
Expires	NNP	O
:	NNP	O
October	NNP	O
15	NNP	O
,	NNP	O
2013	NNP	O
EX	NN	O
-	NN	O
24	NN	O
7	NN	O
etn12312013ex24	NN	O
.	NN	O

htm	NN	O
EXHIBIT	NN	O
24	NN	O
Eaton	NN	COMP
Corporation	NN	COMP
plc	NN	COMP
2013	NN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
Item	NN	O
15	NN	O
(	NN	O
b	NN	O
)	NN	O
Exhibit	NN	O
24	NN	O
Power	NN	O
of	IN	O
Attorney	NN	O
KNOW	NNP	O
ALL	DT	O
MEN	NN	O
BY	NN	O
THESE	NN	O
PRESENTS	NN	O
:	NN	O
That	DT	O
each	DT	O
person	NN	O
whose	WP$	O
name	NN	O
is	VBZ	O
signed	VBZ	O
below	IN	O
has	IN	O
made	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
constituted	VBN	O
and	CC	O
appointed	CC	O
,	CC	O
and	CC	O
by	IN	O
this	DT	O
instrument	NN	O
does	VBZ	O
make	VB	O
,	VB	O
constitute	NN	O
and	CC	O
appoint	NN	O
Richard	NN	PER
H	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Fearon	NN	PER
,	NN	O
Ken	NNP	PER
.	NN	PER
D	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Semelsberger	NN	PER
or	CC	O
William	NN	PER
E	NN	PER
.	NN	PER
Myers	NN	PER
his	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
true	JJ	O
and	CC	O
lawful	JJ	O
attorney	NN	O
,	NN	O
for	IN	O
him	PRP	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
and	CC	O
in	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
name	NN	O
,	NN	O
place	NN	O
and	CC	O
stead	NN	O
to	TO	O
subscribe	NN	O
,	NN	O
as	IN	O
attorney-in-fact	IN	O
,	IN	O
his	PRP$	O
or	CC	O
her	PRP$	O
signature	NN	O
as	IN	O
Director	NN	O
or	CC	O
Officer	NN	O
or	CC	O
both	DT	O
,	DT	O
as	IN	O
the	DT	O
case	NN	O
may	MD	O
be	VB	O
,	VB	O
of	IN	O
Eaton	IN	O
Corporation	NN	O
plc	NN	O
,	NN	O
to	TO	O
its	PRP$	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
for	IN	O
the	DT	O
year	NN	O
ended	VBN	O
December	VBN	O
31	VBN	O
,	VBN	O
2013	VBN	O
pursuant	NN	O
to	TO	O
the	DT	O
Securities	DT	O
Exchange	NNP	O
Act	NNP	O
of	IN	O
1934	IN	O
,	IN	O
and	CC	O
to	TO	O
any	DT	O
and	CC	O
all	DT	O
amendments	DT	O
to	TO	O
that	IN	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
,	NN	O
hereby	NN	O
giving	VBG	O
and	CC	O
granting	CC	O
unto	NN	O
each	DT	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
full	JJ	O
power	NN	O
and	CC	O
authority	NN	O
to	TO	O
do	VB	O
and	CC	O
perform	NN	O
every	DT	O
act	NN	O
and	CC	O
thing	NN	O
whatsoever	NN	O
necessary	JJ	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
done	VBN	O
in	IN	O
the	DT	O
premises	DT	O
,	DT	O
as	IN	O
fully	RB	O
as	IN	O
he	PRP	O
or	CC	O
she	PRP	O
might	MD	O
or	CC	O
could	MD	O
do	VB	O
if	IN	O
personally	RB	O
present	NN	O
,	NN	O
hereby	NN	O
ratifying	NN	O
and	CC	O
confirming	VBG	O
all	DT	O
that	IN	O
each	DT	O
such	JJ	O
attorney-in-fact	JJ	O
shall	MD	O
lawfully	RB	O
do	VB	O
or	CC	O
cause	NN	O
to	TO	O
be	VB	O
done	VBN	O
by	IN	O
virtue	NN	O
hereof	NN	O
.	NN	O

This	DT	O
Power	NN	O
of	IN	O
Attorney	NN	O
shall	MD	O
not	RB	O
apply	VB	O
to	TO	O
any	DT	O
Annual	JJ	O
Report	NN	O
on	IN	O
Form	NN	O
10	NN	O
-	NN	O
K	NNP	O
or	CC	O
amendment	NN	O
thereto	NN	O
filed	NN	O
after	IN	O
December	IN	O
31	IN	O
,	IN	O
2014	IN	O
.	IN	O

IN	NN	O
WITNESS	NNP	O
WHEREOF	NN	O
,	NN	O
this	DT	O
Power	NN	O
of	IN	O
Attorney	NN	O
has	NN	O
been	VBN	O
signed	VBN	O
at	IN	O
Cleveland	IN	O
,	IN	O
Ohio	IN	O
,	IN	O
U.S.A	IN	O
.	IN	O
